I have an email list
that I've written four months of emails,
each one delivering
a helpful fact and trick and tip
when it comes to nutrition to help people
lose
fat, get in shape, whatever.
All they need to do is sign them up.
And again,
over that four-month period of time,
I guarantee, and the data
shows, that a lot of people join
that just because they want the value from
the
emails.
But over the course of months of being
helped every day, they're getting
warmed up, as we use in sales terminology.
They start as a cold lead,
and the automations day by day warm them
up to the point
they're like, "Do you know what?
This guy's turned up for me every single
day with
a tip.
He's obviously pre-written these emails
for months.
I'm going to join his program because no
one else is." Again, these autoresponders
can be to do with anything. Even if,
let's say, you're a judo instructor
and you
recorded a course on the uchi mata,
which is a type of
throw for any of you not in jujitsu.
You could then be like, "Hey, guys.
I've got an instructional here to help you
with hip throws." Every day, you'll get
emailed a certain tip or trick or setup,
whatever it is.
It's completely free.
Then over those days,
they could get all of that value by
email, and on the last day you go, "Look,
I've actually put this all into a course
and I've saved the best bits for it.
It's only X amount.
Buy now." If you were to teach languages,
you could say, "Over the next 100 days,
I'm going to teach you 100 things
that you can do to speak French, not
fluently, but to the level that
when you next go to France
or a French-speaking
country,
you'll be able to navigate the world of
speaking a foreign language." Oh,
cool. It's free as well.
Then those people start learning little
bits of French
over that 100 days,
and then before they know it,
they're at a restaurant.
"Oh, "... "
And they're like,
"Wow." Then they get engaged.
"If you would like to speak French
fluently, I have an online course.
It'll take you three to six months
and it costs this." They go, "Oh,
do you know
what? I'm already one foot in."
And this doesn't have to be everyone.
If 100 people join your list, if five buy,
it's better than the ratios you were
getting from sending them to the website